IBT0056
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Communications Department Videocassettes
1980-2000
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0056
100 Cubic Feet Records center cartons containing videotape cassettes
- Video Cassettes, Series 1
  - Teamste WBBM News, May 20, 1996; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Ron Carey President, Teamsters Union National Press Club Luncheon, September 23, 1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - 1. World News, CNN; 2. Ten O'Clock; WTTG; 3. News 4, WRC; 4. News 7, WJLA; 5. Eyewitness, WUSA; 6. fox morning, WTTG All segments on Teamsters President Ron Carey, ND; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 1. World News, CNN; 2. Ten O'Clock; WTTG; 3. News 4, WRC; 4. News 7, WJLA; 5. Eyewitness, WUSA; 6. fox morning, WTTG All segments on Teamsters President Ron Carey; BETA cassette, ND; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Ron Carey Interview; BETA Cassette, September 25, 1997; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - The New Teamster Carey Inaugural Tape #2; BETA Cassette, November 25, 1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Jacob Javitts Center: Inside City Hall NY1, March 16, 1995; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - National Press Club, C-SPAN, September 23, 1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Ron Carey, ABC-TV World News Tonight; WETA-TV McNell/Lehrer, December 13, 1991; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters Inauguration 2/1/92, "Camera B" Part 2, Broadcast Tape, February 20, 1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - "Carey inauguration" Tape 2, Broadcast Tape, February 19,1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Teamsters President Ron Carey, Speech Excerpts and B-Roll with Members, Beta SP cassette, 1996; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Ron Carey, Teamsters Strike; goo Morning America, WJLA TV; Fox morning News, WTTG TV, April 6, 1994; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Ron Carey, Teamsters Strike; goo Morning America, WJLA TV; Fox morning News, WTTG TV; Broadcast Tape, April 6, 1994; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Eyewitness News, WATE TV; Broadcast Tape, March 10, 1994; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - "Carey Inauguration" Tape 3; Broadcast Tape, February 19, 1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Teamsters Inauguration 2/1/92 "Camera B" Part 1; Broadcast Tape, February 20, 1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Ron Carey/Teamsters: McNeil/Lehrer News hour, WETA TV (PBS), April 7, 1994; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Teamsters Inauguration 2/1/92, "Camera A"; Broadcast Tape, February 20, 1992; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Full Program: Ron Carey, President of Teamsts, Et Al, May 15, 1994; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 20)